Keep running along, watch as we pass by,
as we raise our flag, up high in the sky.
Alright,
here we go now, sailing through the
endless ocean, facing all that comes by.
Let's look for our treasure nobody has
ever got to witness with their own eyes.
All we have to do is keep believing in our
dreams, And let our heart lead the way!
Then once we got all the
others left is to go,
When we face the dark and stormy weather?
Keep the pace, we'll
link our hearts together!
Then I'm sure we'll make it through!
No matter what!
Keep running along, keep running along!
Start raising our flag as we journey on!
Though our chances are close to
none, We won't back down from anyone!
Let's start off the chase,
let's start off the chase!
Toward our own dreams,
while keeping the pace!
With a compass pointing to our goal!
We won't stop till we've
gone around the world!
Start me up!
Keep running along, keep running along!
And we'll never stop,
till we're at the top!
There's no way that we'll ever quit!
Won't keep heading for tomorrow!
Let's start up the chase!
I see through your eyes!
What we'll have to face!
All the memories we'll say in our hearts!
We'll never let them go!
Brand new world!
Let's start me up!
What's Mosshead doing up there?
He's going to bring the
whole damn tower down.
Who wrote this?
It says Gates of Justice.
Guess I might as well follow it.
Nami and Usopp are probably
on their way to Robin already.
If this is the key they need,
I can't keep them waiting!
Better hurry.
Can't you move any faster?
This is it!
At long last, the bridge of hesitation!
Look, Nico Robin!
That's right.
The Gates of Justice are opening.
It took long enough, and I admit
it was scary for a while there,
but I finally made it.
Once I step through those gates,
I'll be the government's hero.
No, I will be a hero to the entire world.
The bridge leading to the
gate is rising as we speak.
Can you hear it?
It's calling out to its hero!
It's beautiful!
A path into the horizon as
radiant as my shining future!
Although, for you it must look like
a path straight to hell, right?
That's what you're thinking, isn't it?
Well, take a good look!
I'm sick of chasing you around damn it
for the last time you can't escape so.
Give it a rest you obstinate cow I'm
the hero of the entire world and that?
Means I'm different than
you, better than you!
Have I finally gotten that
through your thick skull?
Or do I need to keep
grinding it in for you?
Luffy, everyone, I still believe in you.
Come on, hurry, hurry!
There's no point if I
don't make it in time!
Is that the exit?
Ten minutes until we arrive.
All hands are ready, sir.
All ships confirm positions
and prepare for attack.
Yes, sir!
Now get up!
Show some dignity.
You're not going to ruin this for me.
Did I make it?
Whoa!
Calm down, straw-head!
Huh, it's freaky!
I got enough jerks to deal with!
Get lost!
What?
You mean you're still playing
tough after all we've been through?
We're bros now!
Just deal with it!
Lucci, huh?
You giving you a hard time or something?
By the way, I brought you two keys.
Well, I guess Robin's not here.
Should I lend you a hand?
No.
Leave this guy to me.
You should go after Robin.
You can get to the Gates of Justice
through that door behind the pigeon guy.
Robin left a while back so
we're running out of time!
Keep going and don't look back.
You can super count on me brother.
Listen, just so we're straight here,
despite my appearance, I prefer meat.
Well, just so we're straight
here, I really don't give a damn.
Anyway, enough small talk.
I gotta get that key.
If I can't make it in time,
this is all for nothing.
Two-sword style. Nigiri.
Are you supposed to get stronger when
you wear that bandana on your head?
Let's find out.
Tower climb!
I can't!
Flash!
Triple!
You've given yourself a blind spot.
Giraffe Scythe!
Iron body, edgewise.
What?
There's no blind spots.
on a square.
So what?
If he can't move, who cares?
You're so naive.
Perhaps I should remind you of something.
Yeah?
Unlike humans,
giraffes have four legs.
Tempest kick!
Are you gonna fight me or just sit there?
What do you mean?
Take a look.
My attack has already begun.
First, the slashes go up.
They deflect off the ceiling.
And then finally, they come raining down?
Giraffe shower!
Iron body.
There's too many.
A nose pistol!
Bastard.
You're quite resilient for a
human, but I'm a giraffe boy.
That's your superhero name, Giraffe Boy?
Giraffe Boy?
It's just giraffe, fool.
Now it's giraffe fool?
You're the fool.
I'm the giraffe. Got it?
Listen to yourself, hmm?
Who the hell cares if you're
giraffe boy or whatever?
If you're a swordsman, then
let your blade speak for you.
If you think you can get under my
skin, you're just wasting your time.
I'm not getting under your skin.
I'm gonna cut straight through it.
And if you use your iron body,
I'll cut through that too.
One sword style.
Sword draw.
Lion.
Song!
Tempest kick!
Dragon cut!
Hmph.
Iron body isn't the issue.
If you can't cut me at all, it doesn't
matter if my body's iron or not.
You're right.
I'll have to take a different approach.
One gorilla.
Two gorilla. Now. Again.
three-sword style a test of strength
this time is it sounds fun to me nose
This is truly a fearsome attack!
You never thought you might lose, did you?
You can't even imagine that
I might be stronger than you.
Well, it's time to wake up.
I'll make you face the truth.
I could say the same thing.
Paper art.
Straw Hat!
Ten-thirty king!
Weapons left!
Shit!
Kum-kum!
Rocket!
What happened?
I'm gone!
Mazooka!
You still haven't seen the true,
wild strength of a giraffe.
Then stop talking and show me already.
It would be my pleasure.
Observe, for this is the power of nature.
Giraffe cannon!
There's nothing natural about that.
Extreme nose pistol!
Giraffe blast!
Extract!
But it's like I said, that neck
of yours is your weak point.
Keep telling yourself that. Tempest kick!
Spinning white blade!
Why don't you worry about your
own weak points instead of mine?
Ha!
What's with this guy?
These attacks just keep getting weirder.
You won't get away next time.
Giraffe cannon!
Dammit!
I pushed my neck in so far, it
made my arms and legs pop out.
What could have messed
up, buddy, have you got?
It's like when you cram dough through a
little hole and it comes out as noodles.
Like a pasta machine.
Pasta machine!
Don't act like you did that on purpose!
A long neck is nice, but long
limbs like these are handy as well.
A pro like me can turn even the most
unexpected situations into fresh opportunities.
Behold as I unleash a devastating
new long-range technique.
Giraffe Blast!
Does the same attack you did before!
I've had enough of this nonsense.
Resort style. Tatsu.
Margellion button!
It's too strong!
Moonwalk!
Now what?
It can't be running away.
Pasta machine!
Thank you for waiting.
Never mind the neck.
If I can control the reach of all four
limbs, my blades will be unstoppable.
Perhaps you were so distracted
by my giraffe powers
that you forgot I'm a master
of the four-sword style.
You've done well thus far,
but this battle is over now.
Even if you have the
power of a wild animal.
Even if you can attack
with a long neck of yours.
Even if you can use a four sword style.
What?
He deflected all four blades?
None of those things will give you
the strength it takes to defeat me.
Three-sword style.
Leopard.
Spinning!
Is he flying at me?
Impossible.
I thought for sure he missed me.
What was that?
Did he somehow predict
which way I would dodge?
Oh, come on.
Don't look so surprised.
The way you fight I find
it hard to believe this
is the first time you've
been touched by a blade?
Well it seems you have a little
something to back up your boast!
I won't underestimate you again
but I'm afraid that one hit is
the best you're going to do.
I have four swords six powers and the
immeasurable strength of a giraffe on my side.
That's an equation for victory
if I've ever heard one.
So don't blink.
This will be over in a flash
Now, Giraffe Flaps!
Damn it!
My neck's like a whip.
Whiplash!
Even faster!
Fierce Smash!
How do you like this? Yes!
Still think you can defeat me?
And now for a taste of
my four-sword style.
Prepare yourself.
Fury Slash!
Here I come.
Barely keep up.
Hey, what's wrong?
All you're doing is blocking.
Give it up!
You don't have what it takes to beat me.
You pirates were sorely
mistaken if you thought
you could defy the world
government and survive.
In the name of justice, a mistake that
severe can only be punished by death.
The same goes for Nico Robbins.
You bastard.
What the hell was that?
He looked like a demon.
A god of war with three
faces and six arms.
That can't be possible.
Was I seeing things?
Your mouth just crossed the line.
Now you're going to
pay, you arrogant freak.
Oh, did I offend you?
Well, if you're tired of hearing me talk,
I'll just end this now with the
same move that crippled this tower.
This will be over in an instant
when I slice you in two.
It's the end of the line.
There's nowhere to run.
This time I'll make my attack
twice as powerful as before.
Yeah you're right it is the end
of the line for you at least.
Demon Aura Nine Sword Style.
Asana
It's that demon I saw before.
Is he making that illusion with
his strength of will alone?
Nice try, but you're too late.
Is it too late for me?
Or for you?
Unless you somehow manage to dodge this
tempest kick, then nothing has changed.
You're all top!
Sky Slicer!
That's impossible!
He slashed it into mist!
You did well.
I commend you.
Suffering is welcome on
the path to bloodshed.
Ursula!
Silver Mist!
The End From your other
boss over at Galley Law.
When you see him, I want you
to pass on a message for me.
He said you're all fired.
Paulie.
I see.
Fired, huh?
Too bad it'll be tough.
Assassination skills don't really
come in handy in other lines of work.
You can always get a job at the zoo.
Nice.
That's a good one.
Sorry.
Sorry
Hey Mosshead, did you get a key?
Yeah
Just now got it right here.
That's good news
Seems like you two might have
overdone it a bit, though.
Tower isn't looking so good.
You think it's safe?
Safe enough.
Who cares anyway that's
not important right now?
There you go.
That was the last one.
Now we have all of the keys.
Yeah.
We'd better hurry and get them to rob it.
Run!
Full speed!
Don't stop!
Keep moving no matter what!
We need to save ourselves and distrust
that throwing the Straw Hats will be safe!
We're all gonna make it!
Get off!
So run for your lives!
Even if we break our legs, the
Freaky family ain't stopping!
No!
You can do it!
We're counting on you, Giants!
Listen, guys, if you're just gonna
ride, then try to keep it down!
Hurry, I agree, you're never ready!
Forward!
Go with the beam of helmet!
Shut up!
Granny, hurry!
Faster, faster!
Tiffany, I'm an old woman!
Give me a break here!
Seriously, I'm gonna have
to refuel to keep this up!
Whoa!
Granny, he's gonna fall!
Pull him up!
Oh, jeez!
Who's your demanding today? Granny!
I know, I know!
Hurry, hurry!
Finally the bridge is
connected I can't stop
laughing hey gate guards
is everything ready?
Or what yes sir everything
is in order we're
awaiting your arrival
by the third call that's
Not what I meant the
crew should come out to
salute me their hero
chief Spandam has arrived!
Oh, uh, yes, sir.
We'll be right out.
Idiots, they can't do anything right.
Look, Nico Robin, there it is.
That little gate's the real entrance.
Just a few more steps and we're there.
Once you pass through it, you'll be
crossing the border between heaven and hell.
There's no turning back.
And the moment I drag you past it,
my name will be engraved in history.
Hey hey there witch where
do you think you're going
I know you may not believe
me but I do feel A bit
sorry for you too bad I've
got no say in the matter
there's no reason for you
to live Your death awaits.
You bitch!
I don't want to die.
I want to live!
Stop delaying the inevitable.
You're wasting time.
Get up huh damn it all she won't
budge what's going on here?
You're kidding me she's holding on
to the bridge with her teeth she just
doesn't know when to give up does she
how annoying why the hell are you so
desperate to live don't be so damn
greedy listen to me you're a criminal
understand the only way you can make
the world a better place is by dying!
Why must you be such an annoyance
all the way to the bitter end?
I never thought I would
be so afraid of death.
I want to live.
Please...
Save me!
Luffy!
Finger pistol!
I told you that won't work!
Yellow lotus!
Straw Hat!
No.
Wait, I can't worry about him.
My only concern is getting
through those doors and fast!
It's no use.
There's no way you'll ever get past me.
We'll just have to see
about that, won't we?
Have some straw!
Iron body. Hammer!
No way, he didn't even flinch.
That same punch sent that
chop-a-pop freak flying.
Ah, I see.
You beat Fukuro along the way.
Sorry to break it to you, but my
power level is five times his.
Still, I'm impressed you defeated Fukurou.
Bringing down any agent of CP9
requires superhuman strength.
Whoa, this guy's in a
completely different league.
Now you die.
Gum-Gum!
Jet Pistol!
What the hell? What happened?
And what's with all that steam?
Second gear!
I can't keep my body like this for long.
I'll damn sure stop him so
you go on ahead and hurry.
Robin's waiting right you got it?
I have no idea what you're doing
but keep it up and finish him I
say you'll never get past me didn't
die another guy with Devil Fruit powers?
First things first, time to die.
Shit, what?
Have you forgotten something?
Back in the Galley-La building,
this is the form I was in when I
defeated you with a single blow.
Yeah, sure.
But I was real hungry that day.
Shame!
FINGER PISTOL!
KUM KUM!
IRON BODY!
SHUT THE KUM KUM!
Franky!
You gotta save her!
Stupid woman, don't you get it?
This is useless!
How many times do I have to tell you?
There's no hope for you,
so just give it up now!
I'm not going anywhere.
They're coming.
They're all coming to rescue me!
Just super leave it to me.